

MARINA COBB

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am experienced in object-oriented programming and with developing and debugging code. I am a quick learner and master of new technologies. I work well in both team and self-directed settings. Working several years as a graphic designer, I bring a lot of transferable skills to the table. I am looking to start a new career in technology and broaden my knowledge as a software engineer.

SKILLS & ABILITIES

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Typescript
- React, Angular,
- PGAdmin
- Postman, Codepen, GitHub, Visual Studio
- PostgreSql, Express, Node, REST API's
- WordPress, Squarespace
- Adobe Suites Software
- Layout Design
- Wire framing
- Logical and Analytical Thinking
- Problem-solving
- Written and Verbal Communication
- Perseverance
- Empathy
- Adaptability

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Creative Services Specialist

Early Learning Indiana (Jan 2020 - Present)

As the Creative Services Specialist I use design software to create visual elements such as logos, photography, brochures, videos and illustrations that help deliver a desired message. I design concepts and select colors, images and typefaces to use for marketing purposes. I review creative pieces for errors before printing them.

Graphic Design Specialist

Old Town Design Group (Sept 2016 - Jan 2020)

As the Graphic Design Specialist I assist the marketing team in providing strategic thought and planning to increase brand awareness through external marketing initiatives. In short I am in charge of design and production of branding including logos, websites, landing pages, emails, PowerPoint presentations, photography and videos.

Print Production Artist

PERQ (May 2014 - Sept 2016)

As the Print Production Artist, I efficiently and accurately took a design from conception into a print-ready piece. I reviewed the contents and re-touched layouts in print or digital form and ensured brand standards across font, color, production quality and more.

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Eleven Fifty Academy

Software Engineering

2019 - 2020

Herron School of Art and Design

Bachelor of Fine Arts in Visual Communications

2009 - 2012

CONTACT INFORMATION

cobbmarin@gmail.com | 317.914.2790

marinacobb.github.io/Portfolio/github.com/MarinaCobb